<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Text Repeater</string>
    <string name="type">Type your text here</string>
    <string name="shareApps">Hey, I download an amazing apps, Text Repeater. This app generate repeated message for you, generate blank message and allows to join text before and after.
    \nDownload it from Google Play Store -> </string>

    <string name="text_howmany">How many times to repeat text?</string>
    <string name="text_will_here">Your repeated text will be generate here</string>
    <string name="merge_text_hint">Your marge text will be here</string>

    <string name="howToUseMerge">How to use Join Text Before/After?</string>
    <string name="howToUseRepeat">How to use Repeat Text?</string>
    <string name="howToUseBlank">How to use Blank Text?</string>

    <string name="mergeTextInst">If you would like to add/join multiple text before or after at once time then have to separate the text with comme (,) or line.\n
    For example, if you want to separate with comma (,) then enter text like: Apple,Pineapple,Mango\n
        If you want to separate with line then enter text like:\n
        Apple\n
        Pineapple\n
        Mango\n\nRemember you can only add/join text up to 100 lines in order to running this app smoothly in your device. If you need more text to add/join, follow the process few times.
    </string>
    <string name="repeatedTextInst">Enter the text you want repeat. Enter how many times you want to repeat your text.
        \nIf you select with space, it will put space between two repeated texts. For example: Your Text Your Text Your Text Your Text.\n
        \nWithout space your text will be look like:
        \nYour TextYour TextYourText Your Text.\n\nIf you select new line, it will be generate every text with new line for example:\n
        \nYour Text
        \nYour Text
        \nYour Text
        \nYour Text
\n\nIf you select Vertical space, it will generate vertical space between two repeated texts. For example:

    \n\nYour Text\n\n

    Your Text\n\n

    Your Text\n\n

    Your Text\n

    </string>
    <string name="blankTextInst">Enter how many times you want to generate blank text. You can add lines in your blank text.
        \nRemember that few application such as Facebook messenger or might be other applications, doesn\'t allow to enter blank text. In this case, this will be not our application fault.
    </string>

    <string name="notice">Note: Blank texts cannot be send to few applications because they trim all the blank text before send to the recipient. In this case, this, will be not our application fault.</string>

    <string-array name="servicesTitle">
        <item>Repeated Text</item>
        <item>Blank Text</item>
        <item>Count Text</item>
        <item>Join Text Before/After</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="emailus">storeskapps@gmail.com</string>

</resources>